cyberscoop.com 2019-09-09

# Scoop News Group - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

## Scoop News Group

Scoop News Group (SNG) is the leading public-sector tech media company in the country. Built on a foundation of award-winning journalism, we are the community's platform for education and collaboration through news, TV, radio and events. 

Scoop News Group brings together IT decision-makers and influencers from government, academia and industry every day — online and in-person — to discuss ways technology can transform government and to identify ways to achieve common goals.

## Our Approach to Privacy

If you have any questions regarding privacy, you can contact us at: [hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com](mailto:hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com). SNG works to ensure the security of the information in our trust and we maintain the privacy of our data through appropriate action. We maintain reasonable safeguards that include physical and digital security processes to protect data from loss or misuse, and we limit personnel access of data. 

## Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect use and share information and personal data. SNG operates, or provides access to, interactive events and websites. We operate online and in-person and communicate with readers and attendees through a variety of channels, including, but not limited to, events, emails, newsletters and online content. Our Privacy Policy applies to all personal information collected by SNG, regardless of how it is collected or stored. This Privacy Policy covers information collected through all Scoop News Group websites—CyberScoop, FedScoop, StateScoop, EdScoop, WorkScoop—as well as newsletters and events.

## Information We Collect:

To help SNG understand reader usage, SNG and our third-party service providers (including any third-party content or analytics services) automatically collect certain information from your device or web browser when you interact with our sites. To measure use, our partners may auto-collect data on IP address, browser, mobile device and access time. Our third-party marketing and sales software providers effectively comply with the new requirements under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) that took effect on May 25, 2018.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are files that allow us to recognize your browser/device and maintain a personalized experience throughout multiple browsing sessions.

We use cookies in order to provide you with the best experience on Scoop News Group websites. The information we may collect via cookies includes but is not limited to; the time and date spent on our websites, the duration spent on our website, and how you interact (click and search) within our content. Cookies will be used by Scoop News Group and/or our third-party partners to help deliver relevant content, deliver targeted advertising, provide social media features, and analyze our traffic to improve your experience. Cookies can remain on your device until manually deleted, automatically deleted after you leave the site or until you restart your device. By using our services, you are accepting the practices described above, including our use of cookies, tracking pixels, and similar online tools. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our services.

## Information You Submit:

SNG may collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII) from you or other sources. PII generally means information that might reasonably be used to specifically identify you and may include information such as subscriber data and registered guest data, including name, title, address, email, telephone or ZIP code.

By providing your contact information on a SNG property or by clicking "complete registration" on our event partner registration site, you authorize SNG and its sponsors or partners to contact you with information about events and relevant information for IT professionals. Registered guests and subscribers of SNG properties may be contacted with news, emails, newsletters and event information from SNG and its strategic content and event partners.

## Information We Receive From Other Sources

We combine information we may collect from other sources to increase our ability to provide services to readers and event attendees. Any information we may collect is public information or general consumer and advertiser data.

## Removing, Modifying Your Data:

You may unsubscribe from SNG anytime at [hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com](mailto:hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com) or directly on our sites or newsletters.

## Links:

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third-party website. Our SNG sites may contain links to other websites that we do not control.

## Updates:

If we update the privacy policy, we will notify users on this site.

## Security

We have implemented commercially reasonable security measures to help protect your Personal Data from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access or disclosure. As no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we strive to protect your PII. If you want to unsubscribe, please contact us at [hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com](mailto:hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com).

## International Use of Services Statement

SNG is owned and operated in the United States. As a user of our sites, you should be reasonably aware of the privacy laws in the U.S. You may unsubscribe from SNG anytime at [hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com](mailto:hello@ScoopNewsGroup.com) or directly on our sites or newsletters.

Contact Information:  
Scoop News Group “SNG”  
2001 K St. NW, Suite 1411  
Washington, DC 20006  
Telephone: (202) 887-8001 

Please check back for updates to our policy. Thank you!
